A Guide to the Records of the Scheduling Office of Governor Timothy M. Kaine, 2005-2010
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Scheduling Office Records, 2005-2010
The Library of Virginia
44686
16.7 cu. ft. (18 boxes)
Governor Timothy M. Kaine
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred
Biographical Information
The Scheduling Office schedules the Governor's time. The Scheduling Director assembles all scheduling requests, corresponds with those who seek appointments, consults the Governor's Counselor, representatives from the Communications and Policy offices, and then makes scheduling commitments for the Governor. The Scheduling Office compiles complete background packets for meetings and event forms. Cathy Ghidotti was Scheduling Director during Governor Timothy M. Kaine's administration (2006-2010).
Scope and Content
Records, 2005-2010, of the Scheduling Office of Governor Timothy M. Kaine including card invitations and invitations accepted and regretted. The Card Invitations include the original cards sent to the Governor for events and contain notes on whether the invitation was accepted or regretted, how the response was given (through voice mail, email, letter), and the date it was accepted or regretted. Included are invitations to engagement parties, retirement celebrations, festivals, awards dinners, fundraising campaigns, parades, service awards, church events, community fairs, company jubilees, research conferences, Earth day celebrations, Jamestown 400th anniversary, graduation ceremonies, open houses, concerts, and building grand openings, among others.
The Invitations include mainly emails and letters sent to Governor Kaine for various events, similar to those listed above. For some events a Scheduling Request form is included that contains the name of the event, location, attire, press to attend, staff to attend, event contact information, reason for attendance with background notes, logistical instructions, special remarks, and related attachments, including the agenda. Some of the event invitations have constituent correspondence tracking numbers on them.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically, with miscellaneous materials arranged to the rear.
Contents List
- Invitations, Confirmed, 2005 November-December (Box 1a, Folder 1)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2005 November (Box 1a, Folder 2-3)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2005 December (Box 1a, Folder 4-6)
- Card invitations, 2006 February (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Card invitations, 2006 March (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Card invitations, 2006 April (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- Card invitations, 2006 May (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
- Card invitations, 2006 June (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
- Card invitations, 2006 July (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Card invitations, 2006 August (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Card invitations, 2006 September (Box 1, Folder 15-17)
- Card invitations, 2006 October (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
- Card invitations, 2006 November (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
- Card invitations, 2006 December (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 January (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 February (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 March (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 April (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 May 1-17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 May 18-31 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 June 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 June 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 July (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 August (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 September 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 September 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 October 1-12 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 October 13-31 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 November 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Invitations, Accepted, 2006 November 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 January (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 February (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 March (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 April (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 April (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 May (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 June (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 July (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 August (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 September (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 October (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 November (Box 5, Folder 2-4)
- Invitations, Regretted, 2006 Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 5-9)
- Card invitations, 2007 January (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
- Card invitations, 2007 February (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
- Card invitations, 2007 March (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
- Card invitations, 2007 April (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
- Card invitations, 2007 April (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
- Card invitations, 2007 May (Box 6, Folder 3-5)
- Card invitations, 2007 June (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
- Card invitations, 2007 July (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Card invitations, 2007 August (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Card invitations, 2007 September (Box 6, Folder 11-13)
- Card invitations, 2007 September (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- Card invitations, 2007 October (Box 7, Folder 3-9)
- Card invitations, 2007 November (Box 7, Folder 10-13)
- Invitations, 2007 January (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
- Invitations, 2007 February (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- Invitations, 2007 March (Box 8, Folder 3-6)
- Invitations, 2007 April (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
- Invitations, 2007 May (Box 8, Folder 10-15)
- Invitations, 2007 June (Box 8, Folder 16-18)
- Invitations, 2007 June (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
- Invitations, 2007 July (Box 9, Folder 3-5)
- Invitations, 2007 August (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
- Invitations, 2007 September (Box 9, Folder 8-13)
- Invitations, 2007 October (Box 9, Folder 14-17)
- Invitations, 2007 November (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
- Invitations, 2007 December (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
- Invitations, 2007 undated (Box 10, Folder 7-11)
- Card invitations, 2007 December (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Card invitations, 2008 January (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
- Card invitations, 2008 February (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
- Card invitations, 2008 March (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
- Card invitations, 2008 April (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
- Card invitations, 2008 May (Box 11, Folder 5-7)
- Card invitations, 2008 June (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
- Card invitations, 2008 July (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Card invitations, 2008 August (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Card invitations, 2008 September (Box 11, Folder 12-15)
- Card invitations, 2008 September-October (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Card invitations, 2008 October (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
- Card invitations, 2008 November (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
- Card invitations, 2008 December (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Invitations, 2008 January (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
- Invitations, 2008 February (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
- Invitations, 2008 March (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
- Invitations, 2008 April (Box 12, Folder 14-17)
- Invitations, 2008 May (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
- Invitations, 2008 June (Box 13, Folder 6-8)
- Invitations, 2008 July (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Invitations, 2008 August (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
- Invitations, 2008 September (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
- Invitations, 2008 October (Box 13, Folder 15-17)
- Invitations, 2008 November (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
- Invitations, 2008 December (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
- Invitations, 2008, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Card Invitations, 2009 January (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
- Card Invitations, 2009 February (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
- Card Invitations, 2009 March (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
- Card Invitations, 2009 April (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
- Card Invitations, 2009 May (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
- Card Invitations, 2009 June (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Card Invitations, 2009 July (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Card Invitations, 2009 August (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Card Invitations, 2009 September (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- Card Invitations, 2009 October (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
- Card Invitations, 2009 November (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
- Card Invitations, 2009 December (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
- Invitations, 2009 January (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Invitations, 2009 February (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Invitations, 2009 March (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
- Invitations, 2009 April (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Invitations, 2009 May (Box 15, Folder 15-18)
- Invitations, 2009 June (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Invitations, 2009 July (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Invitations, 2009 August (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Invitations, 2009 September (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Invitations, 2009 October (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Invitations, 2009 November (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Invitations, 2009 December (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Invitations, 2010 January (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Invitations, Misc., School visit requests, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Invitations, Misc., Open invitations, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
- Invitations, Misc., 2006 (Box 16, Folder 12-16)
- Invitations, Misc., 2007 (Box 16, Folder 17-22)
- Invitations, Misc., 2008 (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
- Invitations, Misc., 2009 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Invitations, Misc., Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)